Now, I told you that Jasmine Crockett
was a full-of-shit
Zionist climber.
And y'all said, "Stop bringing down
black women."
I bring down black women who are
bringing down black women.
>> [music]
>> Go out and vote again.
Do not get comfortable
at all. We are living in unprecedented
times. And I can tell you that there is
no one better for this moment for
Missouri 1 to keep his eye on the prize,
which is you, the people, than Wesley
Bell.
Y'all believe me now?
Let me break this down for you.
Wesley Bell
was running for a completely different
office until
the Jewish lobby
until the Israeli lobby came to him and
said, "We're going to give you a bunch
of money for you to run against Cori
Bush
because we don't want her in Congress
because she is pro-Palestinian."
And so, because he's a [ __ ] he did. And
it worked. Cori Bush lost her seat in
Congress. When Wesley Bell
announced his run against me,
it was right after I introduced the
Ceasefire Now uh legislation. Mhm. Um
Wesley Bell said in his speech that he
gave, he wasn't running against me
because
I wasn't doing my job. He wasn't running
against me because I wasn't turning out
enough legislation, you know, because I
was not on the job in some way, cuz he
never called me to say, like, "Hey, sis,
I wish you would do more. I wish you
would do better." You know, never had
that conversation. So,
because he stands 100% with Israel. Mhm.
So, he brought that into this.
Now, y'all know I do not
support electoral politics. I think it's
a bunch of BS. However, this is about
principle.
Cori Bush began as an organizer. She had
to be approached several times to run
for office. This was not a career
decision that she made. It was one that
she eventually felt like was the next
step in her being able to serve the
people. That's a very, very rare
occurrence in politics. She went into
the position as a public servant. She
was ousted.
She is trying to come back
and this Wesley Bell guy is still there
and still funded and supported by the
same folks who got her removed and
Jasmine Crockett brought her BBL having
cuz yes, she did get a BBL having ass up
there to stand and vouch for him.
Because they think you all are so dumb
that if they just put any brown-skinned
neck-waving person up there,
>> I'm not even going to go there. you're
going to vote for them. They're using
your identity against you. They
weaponize the very thing they have used
to keep you down to still keep you down
by keeping you manipulated. Jasmine
Crockett is the shady lady at your job.
Jasmine Crockett is the conniving
auntie. Jasmine Crockett is the frenemy.
She is no different than people that are
in your life. So, it is not about
targeting Jasmine Crockett. It's about
targeting women and people who are
willing to lie and manipulate in order
to get themselves advancement. Big up to
Cori Bush and instead of being mad at me
when I'm telling you the truth, don't
believe the hype.
Turn it up [music] our way.
And we've got to create it.
>> [music]
>> Turn it our way.